name: "CIS 60 - Chapter 6"
questions:
  - question: "What should be considered to find the best value when evaluating digital forensics tools?"
    options:
      - "A) Hardware forensic tools"
      - "B) Software forensic tools"
      - "C) Open-source tools"
      - "D) Command-line applications"
    answer: "C"
  - question: "Which of the following is a type of hardware forensic tool?"
    options:
      - "A) Command-line applications"
      - "B) GUI applications"
      - "C) Software programs"
      - "D) Computer systems"
    answer: "D"
  - question: "What are the five major categories of tasks performed by digital forensics tools?"
    options:
      - "A) Acquisition, validation, extraction, reconstruction, reporting"
      - "B) Identification, preservation, analysis, documentation, presentation"
      - "C) Collection, examination, analysis, reporting, testifying"
      - "D) Seizure, custody, examination, analysis, disposal"
    answer: "A"
  - question: "What is the process of making a copy of the original drive called?"
    options:
      - "A) Extraction"
      - "B) Validation"
      - "C) Acquisition"
      - "D) Reconstruction"
    answer: "C"
  - question: "What is a way to confirm that a tool is functioning as intended?"
    options:
      - "A) Verification"
      - "B) Validation"
      - "C) Extraction"
      - "D) Reconstruction"
    answer: "B"
  - question: "What process proves that two sets of data are identical by calculating hash values or using another similar method?"
    options:
      - "A) Acquisition"
      - "B) Verification"
      - "C) Extraction"
      - "D) Reporting"
    answer: "B"
  - question: "What recovery task is considered the most challenging in a digital investigation?"
    options:
      - "A) Data viewing"
      - "B) Keyword searching"
      - "C) Carving"
      - "D) Data Recovery"
    answer: "D"
  - question: "What process is used to re-create a suspect drive to show what happened during a crime or an incident?"
    options:
      - "A) Acquisition"
      - "B) Extraction"
      - "C) Reconstruction"
      - "D) Reporting"
    answer: "C"
  - question: "What type of report is necessary to perform a forensics disk analysis and examination?"
    options:
      - "A) Acquisition report"
      - "B) Extraction report"
      - "C) Reconstruction report"
      - "D) Forensics report"
    answer: "D"
  - question: "What was one of the first MS-DOS tools used for computer investigations?"
    options:
      - "A) SMART"
      - "B) Helix 3"
      - "C) Kali Linux"
      - "D) Norton DiskEdit"
    answer: "D"
